=== A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md ===

> md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:55:**Abstract**
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:56:
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:57:
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:58:
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:59:We present a pipeline for a 
statistical textual exploration, offering a **stylometry-based expla-**
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:60:**nation and statistical 
validation of a hypothe-**
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:61:**sized partition of a text** . 
Given a parameterization of the text, our pipeline: ( **1** ) detects literary
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:62:features yielding the optimal 
overlap between
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:63:the hypothesized and unsupervised 
partitions,
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:64:( **2** ) performs a 
hypothesis-testing analysis to
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:65:quantify the statistical 
significance of the optimal overlap, while conserving implicit correlations between units of text that are more likely
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:66:to be grouped, and ( **3** ) 
extracts and quantifies
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:67:the importance of features most 
responsible for
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:68:the classification, estimates 
their statistical stability and cluster-wise abundance.
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:69:
  md\A Statistical Exploration of Text Partition Into Constituents The Case of.md:70:

=== A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md ===
> md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:42:**Abstract**
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:43:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:44:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:45:Intelligent learning diagnosis is a critical engine 
of intelligent tutoring systems,
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:46:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:47:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:48:which aims to estimate learners’ current knowledge 
mastery status and predict their
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:49:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:50:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:51:future learning performance. The significant 
challenge with traditional learning diag
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:52:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:53:nosis methods is the inability to balance diagnostic 
accuracy and interpretability.
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:54:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:55:
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:56:Although the existing psychometric-based learning 
diagnosis methods provide some
  md\A Unified Interpretable Intelligent Learning Diagnosis.md:57:

=== AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md ===
> md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:9:**Abstract**
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:10:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:11:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:12:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:13:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:14:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:15:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:16:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:17:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:18:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:19:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:20:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:21:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:22:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:23:
  md\AgenticAI-DialogGen Topic-Guided Conversation Generation for.md:24:

=== Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md ===
> md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:20:**Abstract**
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:21:
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:22:
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:23:Understanding human personality is crucial for 
web applications
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:24:
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:25:such as personalized recommendation and mental 
health assess
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:26:ment. Existing studies on personality detection 
predominantly
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:27:
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:28:adopt a “posts → user vector → labels” modeling 
paradigm, which
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:29:
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:30:encodes social media posts into user 
representations for predicting
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:31:
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:32:personality labels ( _e.g._, MBTI labels). While 
recent advances in large
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:33:
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:34:language models (LLMs) have improved text 
encoding capacities,
  md\Ask, Answer, and Detect Role-Playing LLMs for Personality.md:35:

=== Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md ===
> md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:5:**Abstract**
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:6:
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:7:
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:8:This paper studies Graphical SLOPE for precision matrix 
estimation, with emphasis on its ability to recover both sparsity and clusters of edges with equal or similar
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:9:strength. In a fixed-dimensional regime, we establish that 
the root- _n_ scaled estimation error converges to the unique minimizer of a strictly convex optimization problem
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:10:defined through the directional derivative of the SLOPE 
penalty. We also establish
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:11:convergence of the induced SLOPE pattern, thereby obtaining 
an asymptotic characterization of the clustering structure selected by the estimator. A comparison with
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:12:GLASSO shows that the grouping property of SLOPE can 
substantially improve estimation accuracy when the precision matrix exhibits structured edge patterns.
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:13:To assess the effect of departures from Gaussianity, we 
then analyze Gaussian-loss
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:14:precision matrix estimation under elliptical distributions. 
In this setting, we derive the
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:15:limiting distribution and quantify the inflation in 
variability induced by heavy tails
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:16:relative to the Gaussian benchmark. We also study TSLOPE, 
based on the multivariate _t_ -loss, and derive its limiting distribution. The results show that TSLOPE offers
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:17:clear advantages over GSLOPE under heavy-tailed 
data-generating mechanisms. Simulation evidence suggests that these qualitative conclusions persist in high-dimensional
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:18:settings, and an empirical application shows that 
SLOPE-based estimators, especially
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:19:TSLOPE, can uncover economically meaningful clustered 
dependence structures.
  md\Asymptotic Theory for Graphical SLOPE Precision.md:20:

=== Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md ===
> md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:16:**Abstract**
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:17:
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:18:
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:19:Self-supervised features 
are the cornerstone of modern machine learning systems. They
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:20:are typically pre-trained 
on data collections whose construction and curation typically require extensive human effort. This manual process has 
some limitations similar to those
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:21:encountered in supervised 
learning, e.g., the crowd-sourced selection of data is costly and
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:22:time-consuming, preventing 
scaling the dataset size. In this work, we consider the problem
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:23:of automatic curation of 
high-quality datasets for self-supervised pre-training. We posit
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:24:that such datasets should 
be large, diverse and balanced, and propose a clustering-based
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:25:approach for building ones 
satisfying all these criteria. Our method involves successive and
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:26:hierarchical applications 
of _k_ -means on a large and diverse data repository to obtain clusters that distribute uniformly among data concepts, 
followed by a hierarchical, balanced
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:27:sampling step from these 
clusters. Extensive experiments on three different data domains
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:28:including web-based 
images, satellite images and text show that features trained on our
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:29:automatically curated 
datasets outperform those trained on uncurated data while being on
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:30:par or better than ones 
trained on manually curated data.
  md\Automatic Data Curation for Self-Supervised Learning A Clustering-Based Approach.md:31:

=== AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md ===
> md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:14:**Abstract**
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:15:
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:16:
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:17:Product attribute extraction in e-commerce is
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:18:bottlenecked by ontologies that are inconsistent, 
incomplete, and costly to maintain. We
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:19:present **AutoPKG**, a multi-agent Large Language 
Model (LLM) framework that automatically constructs a Product-attribute Knowledge
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:20:Graph (PKG) from multimodal product content. AutoPKG 
induces product types and typespecific attribute keys on demand, extracts attribute values from text and images, and 
consolidates updates through a centralized decision agent that maintains a globally consistent
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:21:canonical graph. We also propose an **evalu-**
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:22:**ation** **protocol** for dynamic PKGs that measures 
type/key validity and consolidation quality, as well as edge-level accuracy for value
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:23:assertions after canonicalization. On a large
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:24:real-world marketplace catalog **dataset from**
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:25:**Lazada (Alibaba)**, AutoPKG achieves up to
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:26:0.953 Weighted Knowledge Efficiency (WKE)
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:27:for product types, 0.724 WKE for attribute
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:28:keys, and 0.531 edge-level _F_ 1 for multimodal
  md\AutoPKG An Automated Framework for Dynamic E-commerce.md:29:value extraction. Across three public benchmarks, we 
improve edge-level exact-match _F_ 1

=== Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md ===
> md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:11:_**Abstract**_ **—Processing-in-Memory** **(PIM)** **architectures** 
**offer** **a**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:12:**promising** **solution** **to** **the** **memory** **bottlenecks** 
**in** **data-intensive**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:13:**machine** **learning,** **yet** **often** **overlook** **the** 
**growing** **challenge**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:14:**of** **activation** **memory** **footprint.** **Conventional** **PIM** 
**approaches**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:15:**struggle** **with** **massive** **KV** **cache** **sizes** 
**generated** **in** **long-context**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:16:**scenarios** **by** **Transformer-based** **models,** **frequently** 
**exceeding**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:17:**PIM’s** **limited** **memory** **capacity,** **while** **techniques** 
**like** **sparse**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:18:**attention** **can** **conflict** **with** **PIM’s** **need** **for** 
**data** **locality.** **Existing**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:19:**PIM** **approaches** **and** **quantization** **methods** **are** 
**often** **insuffi-**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:20:**cient** **or** **poorly** **suited** **for** **leveraging** **the** 
**unique** **characteristics**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:21:**of** **activations.** **This** **work** **identifies** **an** 
**opportunity** **for** **PIM-**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:22:**specialized** **activation** **quantization** **to** **enhance** 
**bandwidth** **and**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:23:**compute** **efficiency.**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:24:**We** **explore** **clustering-based** **vector** **quantization** 
**approaches,**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:25:**which** **align** **well** **with** **activation** **characteristics** 
**and** **PIM’s** **in-**
  md\Breaking the PIM Capacity Wall for.md:26:**ternal** **bandwidth** **capabilities.** **Building** **on** **this,** 
**we** **introduce**

=== CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md ===
> md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:14:ABSTRACT
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:15:
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:16:
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:17:Deploying clinical ML is slow and brittle: models that work at 
one hospital often
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:18:degrade under distribution shifts at the next. In this work, 
we study a simple question – can large language models (LLMs) create _portable_ patient embeddings i.e.
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:19:representations of patients enable a downstream predictor 
built on one hospital to
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:20:be used elsewhere with minimal-to-no retraining and 
fine-tuning. To do so, we
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:21:map from irregular ICU time series onto concise natural 
language summaries using a frozen LLM, then embed each summary with a frozen text embedding model
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:22:to obtain a fixed length vector capable of serving as input to 
a variety of downstream predictors. Across three cohorts (MIMIC-IV, HIRID, PPICU), on multiple
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:23:clinically grounded forecasting and classification tasks, we 
find that our approach
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:24:is simple, easy to use and competitive with in-distribution 
with grid imputation,
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:25:self-supervised representation learning, and time series 
foundation models, while
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:26:exhibiting smaller relative performance drops when 
transferring to new hospitals. We study the variation in performance across prompt design, with structured
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:27:prompts being crucial to reducing the variance of the 
predictive models without altering mean accuracy. We find that using these portable representations improves
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:28:few-shot learning and does not increase demographic 
recoverability of age or sex
  md\CAN WE GENERATE PORTABLE REPRESENTATIONS FOR.md:29:relative to baselines, suggesting little additional privacy 
risk. Our work points to

=== Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md ===
> md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:15:**Abstract**
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:16:
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:17:
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:18:In recent years, the proliferation of social 
platforms has drastically transformed the way individuals interact,
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:19:organize, and share information. In this 
scenario, we experience an unprecedented increase in the scale and
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:20:complexity of interactions and, at the same 
time, little to no research about some fringe social platforms. In this
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:21:paper, we present a multi-dimensional framework 
for characterizing nodes and hyperedges in social hypernetworks,
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:22:with a focus on the understudied alt-right 
platform Scored.co. Our approach integrates the possibility of studying
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:23:higher-order interactions, thanks to the 
hypernetwork representation, and various node features such as user activity,
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:24:sentiment, and toxicity, with the aim to define 
distinct user archetypes and understand their roles within the network.
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:25:Utilizing a comprehensive dataset from 
Scored.co, we analyze the dynamics of these archetypes over time and
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:26:explore their interactions and influence within 
the community. The framework’s versatility allows for detailed
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:27:analysis of both individual user behaviors and 
broader social structures. Our findings highlight the importance of
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:28:higher-order interactions in understanding 
social dynamics, offering new insights into the roles and behaviors that
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:29:emerge in complex online environments.
  md\Characterizing user archetypes and discussions on Scored.co.md:30:

=== Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md ===
> md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:17:**Abstract**
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:18:
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:19:
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:20:
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:21:Matthew Wragg
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:22:University of Bristol
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:23:Bristol, United Kingdom
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:24:matthew.wragg@bristol.ac.uk
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:25:
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:26:
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:27:Paul Marshall
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:28:University of Bristol
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:29:Bristol, United Kingdom
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:30:p.marshall@bristol.ac.uk
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:31:
  md\Circadian Phase Locking of Epilepsy Seizures in Wearable Data A.md:32:

=== Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md ===
> md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:46:### **Abstract**
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:47:
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:48:Labelling tissue components in histology whole slide 
images
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:49:(WSIs) is prohibitively labour-intensive: a single slide 
may
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:50:contain tens of thousands of structures—cells, nuclei, and
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:51:other morphologically distinct objects—each requiring 
manual
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:52:boundary delineation and classification. We present a 
cloudnative, end-to-end pipeline that automates this process through
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:53:a _cluster-first_ paradigm. Our system tiles WSIs, 
filters out tiles
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:54:deemed unlikely to contain valuable information, segments
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:55:tissue components with Cellpose-SAM (including cells, 
nuclei,
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:56:and other morphologically similar structures), extracts 
neural
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:57:embeddings via a pretrained ResNet-50, reduces 
dimensionality with UMAP, and groups morphologically similar objects
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:58:using DBSCAN clustering. Under this paradigm, a human
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:59:annotator labels representative clusters rather than 
individual
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:60:objects, reducing annotation effort by orders of 
magnitude. We
  md\Cluster-First Labelling An Automated Pipeline for.md:61:evaluate the pipeline on 3,696 tissue components across 13

=== CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md ===
> md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:22:**Abstract**
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:23:
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:24:
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:25:We present CLUSTSEG, a general, transformerbased framework 
that tackles different image segmentation tasks ( _i.e_ ., superpixel, semantic, instance, and panoptic) through a 
unified, neural clusteringscheme.Regardingqueriesasclustercenters,
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:26:CLUSTSEG is innovative in two aspects:xcluster
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:27:centers are initialized in heterogeneous ways so as
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:28:to pointedly address task-specific demands ( _e.g_ .,
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:29:instance- or category-level distinctiveness), yet
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:30:without modifying the architecture; and y pixelcluster 
assignment, formalized in a cross-attention
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:31:fashion, is alternated with cluster center update, yet
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:32:without learning additional parameters. These innovations 
closely link CLUSTSEG to EM clustering and make it a transparent and powerful framework that yields superior results 
across the above
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:33:segmentation tasks.
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:34:
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:35:
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:36:**1. Introduction**
  md\CLUSTSEG Clustering for Universal Segmentation.md:37:

=== Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md ===
> md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:21:**Abstract**
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:22:
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:23:
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:24:Quantum computing, with its ability to do exponentially 
faster computation
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:25:compared to classical systems, has found novel 
applications in various fields such
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:26:as machine learning and recommendation systems. Quantum 
Machine Learning
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:27:(QML), which integrates quantum computing with machine 
learning techniques,
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:28:presents powerful new tools for data processing and 
pattern recognition. This
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:29:paper proposes a hybrid recommendation system that 
combines Quantum Hopfield Associative Memory (QHAM) with deep neural networks to improve the
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:30:extraction and classification on the MovieLens 1M 
dataset. User archetypes are
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:31:clustered into multiple unique groups using the K-Means 
algorithm and converted into polar patterns through the encoder’s activation function. These polar
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:32:patterns are then integrated into the variational 
QHAM-based hybrid recommendation model. The system was trained using the MSE loss over 35 epochs in
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:33:an ideal environment, achieving an ROC value of 0.9795, 
an accuracy of 0.8841,
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:34:and a F-1 Score of 0.8786. Trained with the same number 
of epochs in a noisy
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:35:environment using a custom Qiskit AER noise model 
incorporating bit-flip and
  md\Collaborative Filtering using Variational Quantum.md:36:readout errors with the same probabilities as in real 
quantum hardware, achieves

=== DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md ===
> md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:70:**ABSTRACT**
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:71:
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:72:
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:73:
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:74:[Angus G. Forbes](https://orcid.org/0000-0002-8700-7795)
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:75:Purdue University
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:76:West Lafayette, IN, USA 47907
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:77:```
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:78: agforbes@purdue.edu
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:79:
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:80:```
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:81:
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:82:
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:83:Ocean scientists studying diverse organisms and phenomena 
increasingly rely on imaging devices
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:84:for their research. These scientists have many tools to 
collect their data, but few resources for
  md\DESIGNING OCEAN VISION AI AN INVESTIGATION OF.md:85:automated analysis. In this paper, we report on discussions 
with diverse stakeholders to identify

=== Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md ===
> md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:16:**Abstract**
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:17:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:18:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:19:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:20:[Runhao Jiang](https://orcid.org/0009-0000-4841-9175)
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:21:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:22:Hong Kong Baptist University
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:23:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:24:Hong Kong SAR, China
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:25:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:26:csrhjiang@comp.hkbu.edu.hk
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:27:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:28:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:29:**Keywords**
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:30:
  md\Effective Clustering for Large Multi-Relational Graphs.md:31:

=== Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md ===
> md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:32:**Abstract**
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:33:
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:34:**Background:** 
Large language models (LLMs) enable patient-facing conversational
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:35:agents, creating 
a plausible pathway toward patient digital twins that can capture older
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:36:adults’ lived 
experiences, beliefs, and behavioral responses across time. A central barrier to
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:37:clinical-grade 
digital twins is personality drift—inconsistent trait expression across repeated,
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:38:longitudinal 
interactions—which can undermine the reliability of generated trajectories and
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital 
Twins.md:39:intervention-response simulation in geriatric care contexts.
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:40:
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:41:**Objective:** 
To develop ELDER-SIM as a multi-role elderly-care conversational
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:42:platform 
oriented toward building personality-stable elderly digital twin agents, and to
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:43:propose a 
psychometric validation framework for quantifying and improving personality
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:44:consistency in 
LLM-based agents across repeated interactions.
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:45:
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:46:**Methods:** 
ELDER-SIM was implemented using n8n workflow orchestration with local
  md\Elder-Sim A Psychometrically Validated PlatformforPersonality-Stable Elderly Digital Twins.md:47:LLM inference 
(Ollama/vLLM), integrating (1) Big Five (OCEAN) trait specifications, (2) a

=== Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md ===
> md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:10:**Abstract**
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:11:
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:12:
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:13:Machine learning has become a central 
research area, with
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:14:increasing attention devoted to 
explainable clustering, also
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:15:known as conceptual clustering, which is 
a knowledge-driven
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:16:unsupervised learning paradigm that 
partitions data into _θ_ disjoint clusters, where each cluster is described by an explicit
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:17:symbolic representation, typically 
expressed as a closed pattern or itemset. By providing human-interpretable cluster
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:18:descriptions, explainable clustering 
plays an important role
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:19:in explainable artificial intelligence 
and knowledge discovery. Recent work improved clustering quality by introducing
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:20:_k_ -relaxed frequent patterns ( _k_ 
-RFPs), a pattern model that
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:21:relaxes strict coverage constraints 
through a generalized _k_  cover definition. This framework integrates constraint-based
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:22:reasoning, using SAT solvers for pattern 
generation, with
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:23:combinatorial optimization, using 
Integer Linear Programming (ILP) for cluster selection. Despite its effectiveness,
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:24:this approach suffers from a critical 
limitation: multiple distinct _k_ -RFPs may induce identical _k_ -covers, leading to redundant symbolic 
representations that unnecessarily enlarge
  md\Enhancing Clustering An Explainable Approach via Filtered Patterns.md:25:the search space and increase 
computational complexity during cluster construction. In this paper, we address this redundancy through a pattern 
reduction framework. Our contributions are threefold. First, we formally characterize the

=== Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md ===
> md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:13:**Abstract**
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:14:
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:15:
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:16:
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:17:Large language models (LLMs) show promise
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:18:in generating supportive responses for mental
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:19:health and counseling applications. However,
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:20:their responses often lack cultural 
sensitivity,
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:21:contextual grounding, and clinically 
appropriate guidance. This work addresses the gap
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:22:of how to systematically incorporate 
domainspecific, clinically validated knowledge into
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:23:LLMs to improve counseling quality. We 
utilize and compare two approaches, retrievalaugmented generation (RAG) and a knowledge
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:24:graph (KG)–based method, designed to support 
para-counselors. Our KG is constructed
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:25:manually and clinically validated, capturing
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:26:causal relationships between stressors, 
interventions, and outcomes, with contributions from
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:27:multidisciplinary people. We evaluated 
multiple LLMs in both settings using BERTScore
  md\Enhancing Mental Health Counseling Support in Bangladesh using.md:28:F1 and SBERT cosine similarity, as well as

=== Generating consensus and dissent on massive discussion platforms.md ===

=== Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md ===
> md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:13:**Abstract**
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:14:
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:15:
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:16:We consider the linear causal representation learning 
setting where we observe a
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:17:linear mixing of _d_ unknown latent factors, which follow a 
linear structural causal
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:18:model. Recent work has shown that it is possible to recover 
the latent factors as well
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:19:as the underlying structural causal model over them, up to 
permutation and scaling,
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:20:provided that we have at least _d_ environments, each of 
which corresponds to perfect
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:21:interventions on a single latent node (factor). After this 
powerful result, a key open
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:22:problem faced by the community has been to relax these 
conditions: allow for
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:23:coarser than perfect single-node interventions, and allow 
for fewer than _d_ of them,
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:24:since the number of latent factors _d_ could be very large. 
In this work, we consider
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:25:precisely such a setting, where we allow a smaller than _d_ 
number of environments,
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:26:and also allow for very coarse interventions that can very 
coarsely _change_ _the_
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:27:_entire_ _causal_ _graph_ _over_ _the_ _latent_ _factors_ . 
On the flip side, we relax what we
  md\Identifying General Mechanism Shifts in Linear.md:28:wish to extract to simply the _list of nodes that have 
shifted between one or more_

=== Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md ===
> md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:10:_**Abstract**_ **—Generative** **AI,** **particularly** 
**Large** **Language** **Mod-**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:11:**els,** **increasingly** **integrates** **graph-based** 
**representations** **to** **en-**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:12:**hance** **reasoning,** **retrieval,** **and** 
**structured** **decision-making.** **De-**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:13:**spite** **rapid** **advances,** **there** **remains** 
**limited** **clarity** **regarding**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:14:**when,** **why,** **where,** **and** **what** **types** 
**of** **graph–LLM** **integrations**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:15:**are** **most** **appropriate** **across** 
**applications.** **This** **survey** **provides** **a**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:16:**concise,** **structured** **overview** **of** **the** 
**design** **choices** **underlying** **the**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:17:**integration of graphs with LLMs. We categorize existing 
methods**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:18:**based** **on** **their** **purpose** **(e.g.,** 
**reasoning,** **retrieval,** **generation,**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:19:**recommendation),** **graph** **modality** **(knowledge** 
**graphs,** **scene**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:20:**graphs,** **interaction** **graphs,** **causal** 
**graphs,** **dependency** **graphs),**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:21:**and** **integration** **strategies** **(prompting,** 
**augmentation,** **training,**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:22:**or** **agent-based** **use).** **By** **mapping** 
**representative** **works** **across**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:23:**domains** **such** **as** **cybersecurity,** 
**healthcare,** **materials** **science,**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:24:**finance, robotics,** **and** **multimodal** 
**environments,** **we** **highlight the**
  md\Integrating Graphs, Large Language Models, and.md:25:**strengths,** **limitations,** **and** **best-fit** 
**scenarios** **for** **each** **technique.**

=== Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md ===
> md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:9:**Abstract** —In recent years, much of the research on clustering 
algorithms has primarily focused on enhancing their accuracy and
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:10:efficiency, frequently at the expense of interpretability. However, as 
these methods are increasingly being applied in high-stakes
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:11:domains such as healthcare, finance, and autonomous systems, the need for 
transparent and interpretable clustering outcomes has
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:12:become a critical concern. This is not only necessary for gaining user 
trust but also for satisfying the growing ethical and regulatory
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:13:demands in these fields. Ensuring that decisions derived from clustering 
algorithms can be clearly understood and justified is now a
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:14:fundamental requirement. To address this need, this paper provides a 
comprehensive and structured review of the current state of
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:15:explainable clustering algorithms, identifying key criteria to 
distinguish between various methods. These insights can effectively assist
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:16:researchers in making informed decisions about the most suitable 
explainable clustering methods for specific application contexts,
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:17:while also promoting the development and adoption of clustering 
algorithms that are both efficient and transparent. For convenient
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:18:access and reference, an open repository organizes representative and 
emerging interpretable clustering methods under the taxonomy
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:19:[proposed in this survey, available at https://github.com/hulianyu/Awesome
-Interpretable-Clustering](https://github.com/hulianyu/Awesome-Interpretable-Clustering)
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:20:
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:21:
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:22:**Index Terms** —Interpretable Clustering, Algorithmic Interpretability, 
Interpretable Machine Learning and Data Mining, Explainable
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:23:Artificial Intelligence (XAI)
  md\Interpretable Clustering A Survey.md:24:

=== Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md ===
> md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:13:ABSTRACT
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:14:
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:15:
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:16:Learning primitive ( _i_ . _e_ ., 
attribute and object) concepts from seen compositions
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:17:is the primary challenge of 
Compositional Zero-Shot Learning (CZSL). Existing
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:18:CZSL solutions typically rely on 
oversimplified data assumptions, _e_ . _g_ ., modeling each primitive with a single centroid primitive representation, 
ignoring the
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:19:natural diversities of the 
attribute ( _resp_ . object) when coupled with different objects ( _resp_ . attribute). In this work, we develop 
CLUSPRO, a robust clusteringbased prototype mining framework for CZSL that defines the conceptual boundaries of 
primitives through a set of diversified prototypes. Specifically, CLUSPRO
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:20:conducts within-primitive 
clustering on the embedding space for automatically
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:21:discovering and dynamically 
updating prototypes. These representative prototypes are subsequently used to repaint a well-structured and 
independent primitive
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:22:embedding space, ensuring 
intra-primitive separation and inter-primitive decorrelation through prototype-based contrastive learning and 
decorrelation learning. Moreover, CLUSPRO efficiently performs prototype clustering in a nonparametric fashion without 
the introduction of additional learnable parameters or
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:23:computational budget during 
testing. Experiments on three benchmarks demonstrate CLUSPRO outperforms various top-leading CZSL solutions under both
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:24:closed-world and open-world 
settings. [Our code is available at CLUSPRO.](https://github.com/quhongyu/ClusPro)
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:25:
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:26:
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:27:1 INTRODUCTION
  md\Learning Clustering-based Prototypes for Compositional Zero-shot Learning.md:28:

=== Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md ===
> md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:7:_**Abstract**_ **— In** **autonomous** **driving** **and** 
**robotics,** **ensuring**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:8:**road** **safety** **and** **reliable** **decision-making** 
**critically** **depends**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:9:**on** **out-of-distribution** **(OOD)** **segmentation.** 
**While** **numerous**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:10:**methods** **have** **been** **proposed** **to** **detect** 
**anomalous** **objects** **on**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:11:**the** **road,** **leveraging** **the** **vision-language** 
**space–which** **provides**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:12:**rich** **linguistic** **knowledge–remains** **an** 
**underexplored** **field.** **We**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:13:**hypothesize** **that** **incorporating** **these** 
**linguistic** **cues** **can** **be**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:14:**especially beneficial in the complex contexts found in 
real-world**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:15:**autonomous** **driving** **scenarios.**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:16:**To** **this** **end,** **we** **present** **a** **novel** 
**approach** **that** **trains** **a**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:17:_**Text-Driven**_ _**OOD**_ _**Segmentation**_ **model** **to** 
**learn** **a** **semantically**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:18:**diverse** **set** **of** **objects** **in** **the** 
**vision-language** **space.** **Concretely,**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:19:**our approach combines a vision-language model’s encoder with**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:20:**a** **transformer** **decoder,** **employs** 
_**Distance-Based**_ _**OOD**_ _**prompts**_
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:21:**located** **at** **varying** **semantic** **distances** 
**from** **in-distribution** **(ID)**
  md\Leveraging Text-Driven Semantic Variation.md:22:**classes,** **and** **utilizes** _**OOD**_ _**Semantic**_ 
_**Augmentation**_ **for** **OOD**

=== Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md ===
> md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:16:**Abstract**
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:17:
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:18:
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:19:As large language models (LLMs) are increasingly 
integrated into daily life, in roles ranging
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:20:from high-stakes decision support to companionship, 
understanding their behavioral dispositions
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:21:becomes critical. A growing literature uses 
psychometric inventories and cognitive paradigms
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:22:to profile LLM dispositions. However, these approaches 
cannot determine whether behavioral
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:23:differences reflect stable, stimulus-specific 
individuality or global response biases and stochastic
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:24:noise. Here, we apply crossed random-effects 
models—widely used in psychometrics to separate
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:25:systematic effects—to 74.9 million ratings provided by 
10 open-weight LLMs for over 100,000
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:26:words across 14 psycholinguistic norms. On average, 
16.9% of variance is attributable to stimulusspecific individuality, robustly exceeding a statistical null model. 
Cross-norm prediction analyses
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:27:reveal this individuality as a coherent fingerprint, 
unique to each model. These results identify
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:28:individual differences among LLMs that cannot be 
attributed to response biases or stochastic
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:29:noise. We term these differences _machine_ 
_individuality_ . **Keywords:** Artificial intelligence _|_ large
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:30:
  md\Machine individualitySeparating genuine idiosyncrasy.md:31:

=== Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md ===
> md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:10:# **Abstract**
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:11:
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:12:The measurement of human behavior 
remains a central challenge across the behavioral sciences.
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:13:Traditional approaches typically rely 
on passive observation of responses collected under static or
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:14:weakly controlled conditions, 
limiting the identifiability of the underlying generative processes. As a
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:15:result, different behavioral 
mechanisms may produce indistinguishable observations, constraining
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:16:both inference and theoretical 
development.
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:17:In this paper, we propose a 
methodological framework for behavioral measurement based on
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:18:controlled perturbations. From this 
perspective, behavior is conceptualized as the observable output
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:19:of a dynamical system, and 
measurement is reframed as a problem of system identification.
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:20:Experimental environments act as 
measurement instruments that apply structured inputs
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:21:(perturbations) and record behavioral 
trajectories as outputs over time.
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:22:We outline the core components of 
this framework, including the design of perturbations, the role of
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:23:temporal resolution, and the 
integration of multimodal data streams. We further discuss how advances
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:24:in immersive technologies, 
programmable environments, and computational modeling enable the
  md\Measuring Human Behavior Through Controlled Perturbations A Framework.md:25:implementation of closed-loop 
experimental systems, where perturbation, observation, and model

=== Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md ===
> md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:17:**Abstract**
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:18:
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:19:
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:20:AI agents that communicate on behalf of individuals 
need to capture
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:21:how each person actually communicates, yet current 
approaches
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:22:either require costly per-person fine-tuning, 
produce generic outputs from shallow persona descriptions, or optimize preferences
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:23:without modeling communication style. We present 
ASPECT (Automated Social Psychometric Evaluation of Communication Traits),
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:24:a pipeline that directs LLMs to assess constructs 
from a validated
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:25:communication scale against behavioral evidence 
from workplace
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:26:data, without per-person training. In a case study 
with 20 participants (1,840 paired item ratings, 600 scenario evaluations), ASPECTgenerated profiles achieved moderate 
alignment with self-assessments,
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:27:and ASPECT-generated responses were preferred over 
generic and
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:28:self-report baselines on aggregate, with 
substantial variation across
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:29:individuals and scenarios. During the profile 
review phase, linked
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:30:evidence helped participants identify 
mischaracterizations, recalibrate their own self-ratings, and negotiate context-appropriate
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:31:representations. We discuss implications for 
building inspectable,
  md\Mimetic Alignment with ASPECT Evaluation of AI-inferred.md:32:individually scoped communication profiles that let 
individuals

=== On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md ===
> md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:11:_**Abstract**_ **—This** **paper** **studies** **the** 
**information** **theoretic** **secure**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:12:**aggregation** **problem** **in** **a** **three-layer** 
**hierarchical** **network** **with**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:13:**arbitrary** **heterogeneous** **data** **assignment,** **where** 
**clustered** **users**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:14:**communicate** **with** **an** **aggregation** **server** 
**through** **an** **intermedi-**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:15:**ate** **layer** **of** **relays.** **We** **consider** **a** 
**more** **general** **setting** **with**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:16:**arbitrary** **heterogeneous** **data** **assignment** **across** 
**users,** **where**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:17:**‘arbitrary’** **means** **that** **the** **data** **assignment** 
**is** **given** **in** **advance**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:18:**and** **‘heterogeneous’** **means** **that** **the** **users** 
**may** **hold** **different**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:19:**numbers** **of** **datasets.** **Each** **user** **locally** 
**computes** **the** **partially**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:20:**aggregated** **gradients** **as** **its** **input** **based** 
**on** **the** **assigned** **datasets**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:21:**and** **transmits** **masked** **input** **to** **its** 
**associated** **relay.** **The** **relays**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:22:**then** **forward** **the** **aggregated** **messages** **to** 
**the** **server,** **which** **aims**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:23:**to** **recover** **the** **sum** **of** **the** **gradients.** 
**In** **this** **process,** **while**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:24:**some** **users** **may** **drop** **out** **unpredictably,** 
**the** **server** **needs** **to**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:25:**correctly** **recover** **the** **desired** **aggregation** 
**from** **the** **surviving**
  md\On the Optimality of Hierarchical Secure.md:26:**users. Moreover, the server or any relay may collude with a 
subset**

=== Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md ===
> md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:7:**Abstract**
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:8:
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:9:
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:10:AI evaluations have become the primary 
evidence
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:11:for deploying generative AI systems 
across highstakes domains. However, current evaluation
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:12:paradigms often exhibit systemic 
validity failures. These issues, ranging from unjustified design choices to misaligned metrics, remain intractable 
without a principled framework for gathering validity evidence and conducting granular
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:13:diagnostic analysis. In this position 
paper, we argue that **item-level AI benchmark data** is essential for establishing a rigorous science of AI 
evaluation. Item-level analysis enables fine-grained
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:14:diagnostics and principled validation 
of benchmarks. We substantiate this position by dissecting
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:15:current validity failures and 
revisiting evaluation
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:16:paradigms across computer science and 
psychometrics. Through illustrative analyses of item
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:17:properties and latent constructs, we 
demonstrate
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:18:the unique insights afforded by 
item-level data. To
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:19:catalyze community-wide adoption, we 
introduce
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:20:OpenEval, a growing repository of 
item-level
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:21:benchmark data designed supporting 
evidencecentered AI evaluation.
  md\Position Science of AI Evaluation Requires Item-level Benchmark Data.md:22:

=== Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md ===
> md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:9:**Abstract**
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:10:This Monte Carlo simulation examines how prompt engineering 
strategies shape the quality of large
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:11:language model (LLM)–generated personality assessment items 
within the AI-GENIE framework for
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:12:generative psychometrics. Item pools targeting the Big Five 
traits were generated using multiple prompting
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:13:designs (zero-shot, few-shot, persona-based, and adaptive), 
model temperatures, and LLMs, then evaluated
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:14:and reduced using network psychometric methods. Across all 
conditions, AI-GENIE reliably improved
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:15:structural validity following reduction, with the magnitude of 
its incremental contribution inversely related
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:16:to the quality of the incoming item pool. Prompt design exerted 
a substantial influence on both preand post-reduction item quality. Adaptive prompting consistently outperformed 
non-adaptive strategies
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:17:by sharply reducing semantic redundancy, elevating 
pre-reduction structural validity, and preserving
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:18:substantially larger item pool, particularly when paired with 
newer, higher-capacity models. These gains
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:19:were robust across temperature settings for most models, 
indicating that adaptive prompting mitigates
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:20:common trade-offs between creativity and psychometric 
coherence. An exception was observed for
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:21:the GPT-4o model at high temperatures, suggesting 
model-specific sensitivity to adaptive constraints at
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:22:elevated stochasticity. Overall, the findings demonstrate that 
adaptive prompting is the strongest approach
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:23:in this context, and that its benefits scale with model 
capability, motivating continued investigation of
  md\Prompt Engineering for Scale Development in.md:24:model–prompt interactions in generative psychometric pipelines.

=== Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md ===
> md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:36:_**Abstract**_ **—Wine** **tasting** **is** **a** 
**multimodal** **and** **culturally** **em-**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:37:**bedded** **activity** **that** **presents** **unique** 
**challenges** **when** **adapted**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:38:**to** **non-Western** **contexts.** **This** **paper** 
**proposes** **a** **service** **design**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:39:**approach** **rooted** **in** **contextual** **co-creation** 
**to** **reimagine** **wine**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:40:**tasting experiences for Chinese consumers. Drawing on 26 
in-situ**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:41:**interviews** **and** **follow-up** **validation** 
**sessions,** **we** **identify** **three**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:42:**distinct** **user** **archetypes:** **Curious** 
**Tasters,** **Experience** **Seekers,**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:43:**and** **Knowledge** **Builders,** **each** **exhibiting** 
**different** **needs** **in**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:44:**vocabulary,** **interaction,** **and** **emotional** 
**pacing.** **Our** **findings**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:45:**reveal** **that** **traditional** **wine** **descriptors** 
**lack** **cultural** **resonance**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:46:**and** **that** **cross-modal** **metaphors** **grounded** 
**in** **local** **gastronomy**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:47:**(e.g.,** **green** **mango** **for** **acidity)** 
**significantly** **improve** **cognitive**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:48:**and** **emotional** **engagement.** **These** **insights** 
**informed** **a** **partially**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:49:**implemented** **prototype,** **featuring** **AI-driven** 
**metaphor-to-flavour**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:50:**mappings and real-time affective feedback visualisation. A 
small-**
  md\Rethinking Wine Tasting for Chinese Consumers.md:51:**scale** **usability** **evaluation** **(n=10)** 
**confirmed** **improvements** **in**

=== Semantic Distance Measurement based on.md ===

=== Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md ===
> md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:7:**Abstract**
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:8:
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:9:
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:10:Our interaction with others 
largely hinges on how we semantically organize the social world. The organization of such
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:11:conceptual information is not 
static– as we age, our experiences and ever-changing anatomy alter how we represent
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:12:and arrange semantic 
information. How does semantic distance between concepts affect this organization, particularly
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:13:for those with pathological 
deficits in semantic knowledge?
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:14:Using triplet judgment 
responses collected from healthy participants, we compute an ordinal similarity embedding for a
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:15:set of social words and images 
that vary in the dimensions
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:16:of age and gender. We compare 
semantic distances between
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:17:items in the space to patterns 
of error in a word-picture matching task performed by patients with semantic dementia (SD).
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:18:Error patterns reveal that SD 
patients retain gender information more robustly than age information, and that age-related
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:19:errors are a function of 
linear distance in age from a concept
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:20:word. The distances between 
probed and exemplar items in
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:21:the resulting conceptual map 
reflect error patterns in SD patient responses such that items semantically closer to a probed
  md\Semantic distance organizes social knowledge Insights from semantic dementia.md:22:concept– in gender category or 
in linear age– are more likely

=== Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md ===
> md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:11:**Abstract**
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:12:
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:13:
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:14:Personality traits are richly encoded in natural 
language, and large language models (LLMs) trained on human text can simulate personality when
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:15:conditioned on persona descriptions. However, 
existing evaluations rely
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:16:predominantly on questionnaire self-report by the 
conditioned model, are
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:17:typically limited in architectural diversity, and 
rarely use real human psychometric data. Without addressing these limitations, it remains unclear
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:18:whether personality conditioning produces 
psychometrically informative
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:19:representations of individual differences or 
merely superficial alignment
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:20:with trait descriptors. To test how robustly LLMs 
can encode personality
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:21:into extended text, we introduce a round-trip 
evaluation paradigm: we
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:22:condition LLMs on real psychometric profiles from 
290 participants to generate first-person life story narratives, and then task independent LLMs
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:23:to recover personality scores from those 
narratives alone. We show that
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:24:personality scores can be recovered from the 
generated narratives at levels
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:25:approaching human test-retest reliability (mean 
_r_ = 0.750, 85% of the human
  md\Stories of Your Life as Others A Round-Trip Evaluation of.md:26:ceiling), and that recovery is robust across 10 
LLM narrative generators

=== Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md ===
> md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:16:### **Abstract**
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:17:
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:18:
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:19:Talk2AI is a large-scale longitudinal dataset of 
3,080 conversations (totaling 30,800 turns) between
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:20:human participants and Large Language Models (LLMs), 
designed to support research on persuasion, opinion change, and human–AI interaction. The corpus was collected from 
770 profiled Italian
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:21:adults across four weekly sessions in Spring 2025, 
using a within-subject design in which each participant conversed with a single model (GPT-4o, Claude Sonnet 3.7, 
DeepSeek-chat V3, or Mistral
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:22:Large) on three socially relevant topics: climate 
change, math anxiety, and health misinformation.
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:23:Each conversation is linked to rich contextual data, 
including sociodemographic characteristics and
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:24:psychometric profiles. After each session, 
participants reported on opinion change, conviction stability, perceived humanness of the AI, and behavioral 
intentions, enabling fine-grained longitudinal
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:25:analysis of how AI-mediated dialogue shapes beliefs 
and attitudes over time.
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:26:
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:27:### **Background & Summary**
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:28:
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:29:
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:30:Large Language Models (LLMs) increasingly serve as 
routine conversational interfaces for navigating complex information and discussing personal or socio-political 
queries. Alongside this
  md\Talk2AI A Longitudinal Dataset of Human–AI Persuasive.md:31:widespread adoption, researchers have begun 
investigating how repeated interactions with conversational AI shape belief systems and cognitive organization [1, 2]. 
A growing body of evidence indicates that these models can function as persuasive agents, even after brief exposures

=== The Representational Alignment between Humans and Language Models is.md ===
> md\The Representational Alignment between Humans and Language Models is.md:21:**Abstract**
  md\The Representational Alignment between Humans and Language Models is.md:22:
  md\The Representational Alignment between Humans and Language Models is.md:23:

=== The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md ===
> md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:15:**Abstract**
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:16:Psychological scale development has traditionally 
required extensive expert involvement, iterative revision, and large-scale pilot testing before psychometric 
evaluation can begin. The `AIGENIE` R package implements the AI-GENIE framework (Automatic Item Generation with 
Network-Integrated Evaluation),
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:17:which integrates large language model (LLM) text 
generation with network psychometric methods to
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:18:automate the early stages of this process. The 
package generates candidate item pools using LLMs, transforms them into high-dimensional embeddings, and applies a 
multi-step reduction pipeline— Exploratory
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:19:Graph Analysis (EGA), Unique Variable Analysis (UVA), 
and bootstrap EGA— to produce structurally
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:20:validated item pools entirely _in_ _silico_ . This 
tutorial introduces the package across six parts: installation
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:21:and setup, understanding Application Programming 
Interfaces (APIs), text generation, item generation,
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:22:the `AIGENIE` function, and the `GENIE` function. Two 
running examples illustrate the package’s use: the
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:23:Big Five personality model (a well-established 
construct) and AI Anxiety (an emerging construct). The
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:24:package supports multiple LLM providers (OpenAI, 
Anthropic, Groq, HuggingFace, and local models),
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:25:offers a fully offline mode with no external API 
calls, and provides the `GENIE()` function for researchers
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:26:who wish to apply the psychometric reduction pipeline 
to existing item pools regardless of their origin.
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:27:The `AIGENIE` [package is freely available on 
R-universe at https://laralee.r-universe.dev/AIGENIE.](https://laralee.r-universe.dev/AIGENIE)
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:28:
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:29:
  md\The Ultimate Tutorial for AI-driven Scale Development.md:30:**Keywords:** AIGENIE, Generative Psychometrics, 
tutorial, LLMs, AI, EGA, UVA, R package

=== The Umwelt Representation Hypothesis.md ===

=== Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md ===
> md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:8:### **Abstract**
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:9:
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:10:Text clustering is today the most popular paradigm 
for topic modelling, both in academia and
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:11:industry. Despite clustering topic models’ 
apparent success, we identify a number of issues in
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:12:Top2Vec and BERTopic, which remain largely 
unsolved. Firstly, these approaches are unreliable at
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:13:discovering natural clusters in corpora, due to 
extreme sensitivity to sample size and
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:14:hyperparameters, the default values of which 
result in suboptimal behaviour. Secondly, when
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:15:estimating term importance, BERTopic ignores the 
semantic distance of keywords to topic vectors,
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:16:while Top2Vec ignores word counts in the corpus. 
This results in, on the one hand, less coherent
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:17:topics due to the presence of stop words and junk 
words, and lack of variety and trust on the other.
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:18:In this paper, I introduce a new approach, 
**Topeax**, which discovers the number of clusters from
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:19:peaks in density estimates, and combines lexical 
and semantic indices of term importance to gain
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:20:high-quality topic keywords. Topeax is 
demonstrated to be better at both cluster recovery and
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:21:cluster description than Top2Vec and BERTopic, 
while also exhibiting less erratic behaviour in
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:22:response to changing sample size and 
hyperparameters.
  md\Topeax - An Improved Clustering Topic Model with Density.md:23:

=== Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md ===
> md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:11:**Abstract**
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:12:
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:13:
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:14:Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:15:remarkable capabilities across various tasks 
but
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:16:remain prone to hallucinations in 
knowledgeintensive scenarios. Knowledge Base Question
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:17:Answering (KBQA) mitigates this by grounding 
generation in Knowledge Graphs (KGs).
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:18:However, most multi-hop KBQA methods rely
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:19:on explicit edge traversal, making them 
fragile to KG incompleteness. In this paper, we
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:20:proposed a novel graph-based soft prompting
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:21:framework that shifts the reasoning paradigm
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:22:from node-level path traversal to 
subgraphlevel reasoning. Specifically, we employ a
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:23:Graph Neural Network (GNN) to encode 
extracted structural subgraphs into soft prompts,
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:24:enabling LLM to reason over richer structural
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:25:context and identify relevant entities beyond
  md\Topology-Aware Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graph with.md:26:immediate graph neighbors, thereby reducing

=== Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md ===
> md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:10:_**Abstract**_ **—Topic** **models** **have** **evolved** **from** 
**conventional**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:11:**Bayesian** **probabilistic** **models** **to** **recent** **Neural** 
**Topic** **Models**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:12:**(NTMs).** **Although** **NTMs** **have** **shown** **promising** 
**performance**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:13:**when trained and tested on a specific corpus, their generalisation**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:14:**ability** **across** **corpora** **has** **yet** **to** **be** 
**studied.** **In** **practice,** **we** **often**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:15:**expect** **that** **an** **NTM** **trained** **on** **a** **source** 
**corpus** **can** **still** **produce**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:16:**quality topical representation (i.e., latent distribution over 
topics)**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:17:**for** **the** **document** **from** **different** **target** 
**corpora** **to** **a** **certain**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:18:**degree.** **In** **this** **work,** **we** **aim** **to** **improve** 
**NTMs** **further** **so** **that**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:19:**their** **representation** **power** **for** **documents** 
**generalises** **reliably**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:20:**across corpora and tasks. To do so, we propose to enhance NTMs**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:21:**by** **narrowing** **the** **semantic** **distance** **between** 
**similar** **documents,**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:22:**with** **the** **underlying** **assumption** **that** **documents** 
**from** **different**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:23:**corpora** **may** **share** **similar** **semantics.** 
**Specifically,** **we** **obtain**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:24:**a** **similar** **document** **for** **each** **training** 
**document** **by** **text** **data**
  md\Towards Generalising Neural Topical.md:25:**augmentation.** **Then,** **we** **optimise** **NTMs** **further** 
**by** **minimising**

=== Transformer Semantic Genetic Programming.md ===

=== Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md ===
> md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:9:**Abstract**
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:10:
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:11:
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:12:Prompt sensitivity, which refers to how strongly
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:13:the output of a large language model (LLM) depends on the exact 
wording of its input prompt,
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:14:raises concerns among users about the LLM’s
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:15:stability and reliability. In this work, we consider LLMs as 
multivariate functions and perform a first-order Taylor expansion, thereby
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:16:analyzing the relationship between meaningpreserving prompts, their 
gradients, and the
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:17:log probabilities of the model’s next token.
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:18:We derive an upper bound on the difference
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:19:between log probabilities using the CauchySchwarz inequality. We show 
that LLMs do
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:20:not internally cluster similar inputs like smaller
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:21:neural networks do, but instead disperse them.
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:22:This dispersing behavior leads to an excessively high upper bound on 
the difference of log
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:23:probabilities between two meaning-preserving
  md\Understanding the Prompt Sensitivity.md:24:prompts, making it difficult to effectively reduce to 0. In our 
analysis, we also show which

=== User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md ===
> md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:88:of this work owned by others than ACM 
must be honored. Abstracting with credit is permitted. To copy otherwise, or republish, to post on servers or
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:89:to redistribute to lists, requires prior 
specific permission and/or a fee. Request permissions from permissions@acm.org.
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:90:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:91:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:92:© 2018 Association for Computing 
Machinery.
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:93:Manuscript submitted to ACM
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:94:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:95:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:96:1
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:97:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:98:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:99:Conference acronym ’XX, June 03–05, 2018, 
Woodstock, NY Kumar et al.
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:100:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:101:
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:102:During the COVID-19 pandemic, Telegram 
saw a significant rise in popularityin Singapore, becoming a major venue
  md\User Archetypes and Information Dynamics on Telegram COVID-19 and.md:103:

=== Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md ===
> md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:14:**Abstract.** Explaining Machine Learning (ML) results in a 
transparent
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:15:and user-friendly manner remains a challenging task of 
Explainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI). In this paper, we present a method to enhance
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:16:the interpretability of ML models by using a Knowledge Graph 
(KG). We
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:17:store domain-specific data along with ML results and their 
corresponding explanations, establishing a structured connection between domain
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:18:knowledge and ML insights. To make these insights accessible to 
users,
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:19:we designed a selective retrieval method in which relevant 
triplets are extracted from the KG and processed by a Large Language Model (LLM)
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:20:to generate user-friendly explanations of ML results. We 
evaluated our
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:21:method in a manufacturing environment using the XAI Question Bank.
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:22:Beyond standard questions, we introduce more complex, tailored 
questions that highlight the strengths of our approach. We evaluated 33 questions, analyzing responses using 
quantitative metrics such as accuracy
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:23:and consistency, as well as qualitative ones such as clarity and 
usefulness.
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:24:Our contribution is both theoretical and practical: from a 
theoretical
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:25:perspective, we present a novel approach for effectively enabling 
LLMs
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:26:to dynamically access a KG in order to improve the explainability 
of
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:27:ML results. From a practical perspective, we provide empirical 
evidence
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:28:showing that such explanations can be successfully applied in 
real-world
  md\Using Large Language Models and Knowledge.md:29:manufacturing environments, supporting better decision-making in 
manufacturing processes.

=== Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md ===
> md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:14:**Abstract**
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:15:
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:16:
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:17:Mental health is not a fixed trait but 
a dynamic process shaped by the interplay between individual dispositions and situational
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:18:contexts. Building on interactionist 
and constructionist psychological theories, we develop
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:19:interpretable models to predict 
well-being and
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:20:identify adaptive and maladaptive 
self-states
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:21:in longitudinal social media data. Our 
approach integrates person-level psychological
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:22:traits (e.g., resilience, cognitive 
distortions, implicit motives) with language-inferred situational features derived from the Situational 8
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:23:DIAMONDS framework. We compare these
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:24:theory-grounded features to embeddings 
from
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:25:a psychometrically-informed language 
model
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:26:that captures temporal and 
individual-specific
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:27:patterns. Results show that our 
principled,
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:28:theory-driven features provide 
competitive performance while offering greater interpretability. Qualitative analyses further highlight the
  md\Who We Are Where We Are Mental Health at the Intersection of Person.md:29:psychological coherence of features 
most predictive of well-being. These findings underscore the value of integrating computational



